A new breeze in the clear skies
Brings in new days enveloped in happiness
A sprouting dream
Shines light on
Our modest life
Things feel even more fun
Than they were yesterday
And my heart races
Along the long path
Even if you stop or grow worried
Take a slow, deep breath
And continue at your own pace
Beautiful life
Every time you walk
You'll find sights you've never seen
New encounters come out of nowhere
When our feelings intertwine
It is surely a sign of irreplaceable
Wonderful days when we all laugh together
It's a beautiful story
Heave-ho!
Now this one's a beauty.
I'll clean it off.
Hup!
All set.
Thanks.
Now then...
Sweet and delicious!
We should make some fresh salad with it.
Could I try some?
Sure, if you don't mind biting the same one.
How is it?
Spicy!
Oh, you took a bite from that end?
Sweet
The pointy end is spicy,
so it's better used making pickles.
Normal
Spicy
You could have warned me!
Sorry.
We can never have too many non-perishables.
Maybe we can make lots of pickles.
I guess we can also make some dried daikon.
How do we do that?
Cut them and dry them, I guess?
Mister Mayor!
Something wrong?
Some weird people are here.
Weird people?
Yup, definitely weird people!
Hi there, Progenitor?
Hmm?
How long has it been? You look well.
Thanks.
Progenitor of Vampires
Valgryfe
You look well enough yourself.
So well you could kill me and I wouldn't die.
Or would I?
I never have, so I truly do not know.
Oh, little Alfred.
How long has it been?
Twenty years, perhaps?
Not even one, actually.
When you live as long as I have,
you lose all sense of time.
Who is this with you?
Your wife?
No, no.
Though I am honored you think as much,
I'm afraid I'm not.
Korin Priestess
Fuushu
My name is Fuushu.
I am but one Korin priestess.
I'm Hiraku, the mayor around here.
What's this Korin religion, though?
Oh, did I never mention it?
The name did come up
when we got that piano, but...
It is essentially a conglomeration
of all the gods and religions
worshiped in these lands.
Our temple teaches that all should
be free to praise their own gods.
That's pretty broad-minded.
The Progenitor leads the Korin religion.
I'd assumed he was someone important,
but that's something else.
And the Great Priestess Fuushu
is someone of such stature that parades
are held to celebrate her presence.
What?
Priestess
We need to hold a bigger reception then!
Your Holiness!
You needn't worry.
It is my fault we pay visit unprompted.
Yes, she has a request of you.
What sort of request?
I ask that you please save my son's life.
Your village is home not only to
the vampire princess Lu Lulucy,
the leading authority in
the study of medicinal herbs,
but also the great Flora Sakutou,
famed seeker of knowledge
and an unmatched apothecary.
You have need of me?
You're that famous, huh?
Not to brag, but the books I write
are used as texts in every
school of magic there is.
Flora Sakutou's Newest Work
Future in Fermentation
Tell me what your son suffers from,
and I will get straight to work.
This will prove difficult.
It's quite a unique case...
A combination of the most
complicated illnesses imaginable.
I feared as much.
Every apothecary and healer
I've visited has said the same.
Difficult even for the greatest, is it?
Isn't there anything we can do?
It won't be easy, but we can't
simply turn them away.
Right. We can figure something out.
They locked themselves in
and set to their research.
I want you to get all
the ingredients listed in here.
Sure thing.
The holy drop is a white flower
that grows on snowy peaks...
Isn't that what this is?
It was brought here for Lu...
I can handle that.
I'll fly right up to get some.
Next is a walking mushroom
that wanders dark forests.
We can handle any business in the forest!
"A treasure so rare few
can even dream of finding it."
That sounds pretty exaggerated.
"It is known as the dragon's tear..."
Tickle-tickle.
Is this really what I need?
Next, we need a dark stone
from the Gurugranth Mountains.
Why does that sound familiar?
Oh, that's probably the thing
in Dryme's lair.
The one in the back that's good
for propping the door open.
Want me to go get it?
If you could.
We have made our return...
Are you all right?!
The wandering mushroom was
more powerful than the stories say.
How does a mushroom even get powerful?
Here it is.
Smaller than I thought.
Here are the ingredients everyone gathered
and a potted plant Michael procured for us.
Impressive as ever.
That's quite a rare plant.
We'll have to be careful as we pull it up.
How many researchers have suffered
so we might know?
Is that one of those things
that screams when you pull it up
and spells bad news for everyone?!
You're just gonna go for it?!
Seems pretty normal to me.
When pulled up, it releases an odor
strong enough to send beasts fleeing.
You simply weren't fast enough.
That... reeks!
Don't worry, it's completely harmless.
You'll just need a bath.
You can handle the rest...
We'd managed to gather all the ingredients,
but the hard part had only just begun.
Now we need to put the lid on, turn it to
the right, and heat for ten seconds!
The angle is off!
Their experimentation went on for days
while Fuushu remained in prayer
from morning until night.
No! You can't let it get away!
It went that way!
Settle down and be burned already!
It's getting pretty late.
You should head inside.
Please pay me no mind.
Praying is all I can do.
Now! Focus all your magic!
Yes! We finally have enough heat!
Five, four...
Three, two, one!
Blast off!
Goodness, is this it?
Thank you!
I'm sure this must have been
a demanding task.
Save your thanks and see your son
takes that right away.
His condition should improve rapidly.
Very well, but I will return
this favor someday!
We will pay visit again soon enough.
Within ten years at the latest.
His sense of time is all off.
Great work, you two.
It's great that you pulled it off.
I'm quite exhausted.
I could write several volumes
about all that we discovered.
Now to handle our remaining issues...
Fuushu's daily prayers left
our statues with a blinding glow.
Whether that was in response
to her love for her child,
or some divine miracle, no one knew.
But its glow lasted through the night,
keeping Zabuton's family awake.
It does feel a tad sacrilegious,
but we decided the doors would stay shut
except during times of prayer.
Farming Life in Another World 2!
Apparently you can cook them.
Wait, really?
It makes them softer and less tart...
Huh?
What?
What kind of tree is that?
I had completely forgotten about
this experimental area.
With the almighty farming tool
the god granted me,
I was able to grow any crop I could imagine.
So long as I could imagine it,
I didn't need to worry about
seeds or anything.
Cumin
Sometimes that led to things growing
in ways I never knew.
Coriander
Peppercorn
Sesame! Sesame! Sesame!
Open sesame!
So that's what sesame looks like?
Sesame
What type of tree is this?
I honestly don't know.
I remember trying to grow new things,
but I don't know which one this is.
I don't want to be too restrictive,
as I know this was all experimental,
but we should keep a record of all the things
we attempt to grow in the village.
We never know what might
get mixed with our other crops.
True.
But what is this?
Look, it bears green fruit.
You're right. Too big to be plums...
Too hard to be kiwis...
These are from that tree, right?
Oh, that's it!
These are probably walnuts!
I'd always thought they
grew looking like this.
Is that the seed?
Probably.
You can eat what's inside.
But they're hard,
so you need special tools.
I've cracked one.
Now that's some power!
Is it safe to eat?
I dunno...
Might be best to cook it.
Walnuts...
This tree is bearing fruit, too.
Smaller than the walnuts.
Looks like there's a seed in this too.
Do we have to break them?
Pulverized!
Oh, that's an almond!
Next is almonds...
If we've got walnuts and almonds,
I think I can figure out the rest.
This doesn't seem to bear any fruit.
Is it some sort of leafy vegetable?
Or maybe some kind of potato?
Not too far from that, actually.
These peanuts grow underground
in the same way.
What an odd shape.
Now we have peanuts...
They look much like beans.
True. I wonder what they technically are.
Walnuts, almonds, and peanuts.
Now it all comes back to me.
Nuts! Nuts! Nuts!
I was dying for a handful of
mixed nuts back then.
Nuts! Nuts! Nuts!
If I'd thought of beer back then,
Beer! Beer! Beer!
I'm sure this would be a field of wheat now.
But if this is the nut field,
what's with that colorful fruit there?
Judging by the color,
perhaps it's a fruit like an apple?
Or maybe something for curry?
That spicy... what was it again?
Chili pepper?
Hmm, doesn't really seem like a pepper.
Given all the nuts we've found,
the answer should be obvious.
There's something
sticking out of the bottom.
The shape nearly gives it away,
but you're still left thinking,
"This can't be how they grow, right?"
Do we eat what's inside this shell too?
How is everyone so strong?
I knew it, cashews.
Never expected them to hang off like this.
Seed?
Fruit
How did they evolve this way?
The fruit was like a sort of astringent mix
between an apple and a pear.
Roast them over a flame
and they come out like this.
They're so pleasantly fragrant.
I'm sure they'd pair well with tea.
These would fly off the shelves
if sold in the Demonic Kingdom.
Good thinking. They're easy to trade
because they keep long too.
I should try growing more new things
when I get the chance.
Oddity Ranking
Tentative 1st Place
I wonder if we'll ever encounter
anything as peculiar as cashews.
Farming Life!
In Another World!
2!
Let me tell you a story about a slime.
Lives near water
Slime
One day, a slime that purified our water
fell into a wine barrel
and transformed into a wine slime.
Specialty: Drunken Breath
Wine Slime
Ever since, that slime would
show up at every event,
trying to get some more to drink.
But we never knew much more about it.
Here goes then!
Okay!
Go!
Nice. That worked well.
Hey, Mayor!
What are you up to?
Testing out a parachute.
What's a parachute?
Something to keep me safe if I ever
accidentally fall off your backs mid-flight.
Why not just land on the ground like normal?
Some of us can't, you know.
That worked well enough,
but I doubt it can handle much weight.
We could make it bigger,
but I bet it will get bulky and tangled.
Huh?
Wine slime?
You want to go for a ride?
I'm not sure it's safe.
Such a low height will be no issue.
You sure?
Out of respect for the wine slime's bravery,
I let it take our first test flight.
Here goes.
Go!
I didn't think it cared about
anything but alcohol,
but maybe it can be our
test pilot from now on.
Huh?
What?!
Are you okay...?
Seems fine, I guess.
Maybe it got bored?
Definitely faster to jump.
It remains a creature shrouded in mystery,
but one thing's for sure-
it's as carefree as they come.
Mountain Elf Workshop
Okay!
Lady Ya.
Assistant Head of the Mountain Elves
Hiterto
I'd like to discuss our production plan.
What do you think? Incredible, right?
Were we not asked to make a standard bowl?
This can hold everyone's food at once!
Bigger things are better than smaller ones!
That didn't work, huh?
I need to make it thicker and stronger.
I'd ask that you make it smaller first...
My name is Hiterto,
and I am Lady Ya's assistant.
The two of us grew up together,
and I was meant to take lead.
However, I felt myself more suited
as an assistant and declined.
This forced Lady Ya to take the role,
but I believe this worked out in the end.
After enduring a great many things,
our people arrived at the Great Tree Village.
I've never seen so much delicious food!
Here we've found fantastic cuisine
and steamy baths.
This water isn't cold!
And sleep now in warm beds.
This doesn't hurt my back!
This may be the first time our people
have ever enjoyed such luxury.
We are ever grateful to the
Great Tree Village for welcoming us in.
But as assistant to my people's leader,
I must also consider how we might
continue enjoying such comforts.
One drink and the world goes round!
Lady Ya does not seem to
concern herself with such thoughts.
What is most important is for our people
to show we benefit the village.
Fortunately, our dexterous nature has
allowed us to make significant contributions.
Now, as for who will handle what...
Equally as important is
our relationship with the mayor,
the village's most important figure.
As far as I can tell, the mayor engages
with all residents on equal grounds.
He does not appear to choose favorites.
But it would serve us well
to earn his favor, regardless.
Thankfully, Lady Ya appears
willing to do just that.
Something wrong?
Is something bothering you?
Ya?
Y-Yes!
Are you okay?
Very okay!
That's good, I guess.
But she's far too obvious.
Well, I mean, I... respect him.
Talking About the Mayor
That settles it, then.
Let's do all we can to earn his favor!
Huh?
I'll assist you!
All right!
How about that?!
How about what?
I've trained this hard to catch
the mayor's attention!
Why?
I went heavier with each attempt.
And now I can lift a boulder this large!
I asked why, not how!
You do not need muscles
to catch his attention.
What?!
Why?!
Haven't we always said a strong physical form
is the way to win over a man?
That's the way to win
a struggle of brute strength!
Got ya!
I can't deny that some of our old stories
talk of things like that,
but that will never serve our purpose
in the Great Tree Village!
You're right...
Because all the other residents
are far stronger.
I saw as much during
the martial arts competition.
But I'll never win him
if I can't defeat them!
We're not trying to capture him!
Maybe it's best to show you what I mean.
What's wrong, Ya?
What did you want to show me?
Go ahead, Lady Ya.
Right...
Well?!
This is the heaviest boulder I've ever lifted.
But I can go heavier!
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
Put that down. It's dangerous!
Now do you understand?
Yeah.
Some things can't be solved with brute force...
There are few things that can be, in fact.
Now then, let's work on other methods.
Okay...
I'll try showing off my incredible abs instead!
Why is it always about muscles with you?!
We need to tackle this head-on.
We'll want to use every weapon
you have to its full potential....
So perhaps we should focus on
those legs and rear.
What are you basing that decision on?!
You know I'm sensitive about that stuff!
This is for the sake of our people.
Then I'll... work on
my chest muscles!
Enough with the muscles!
Lala lalalala...
A white cloud floating in the sky
The dazzling first star of the night
The sun goes down before you know it
Even somewhat gloomy days
Might get you one step closer
Tomorrow should be another good day
As the wind blows gently by
The heart is cleansed
No matter what happens
I can keep at it
As long as you are by my side
Let's sing so we don't forget today
So that we can smile again tomorrow
Even if we cry again sometime
I'll always be by your side
Ready one, two, and three-let's dance!
Who cares if we just watch and learn?
Make bad steps
It doesn't bother me
I want us to sing a song
And leave everyone smiling
We should make these days last forever
Next time
Fine Day for Visitors
Episode 6